<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Music App UI</string>
    <string name="library">Library</string>
    <string name="favorites">Favorites</string>
    <string name="all_songs">All Songs</string>
    <string name="playlists">Playlists</string>
    <string name="radio">Radio</string>
    <string name="playing">Now Playing</string>

    <string-array name="menu_array">
        <item>Recommended</item>
        <item>Library</item>
        <item>Favorites</item>
        <item>Playlists</item>
        <item>Radio</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="action_websearch">Web search</string>
    <string name="app_not_available">Sorry, there\'s no web browser available</string>

    <string name="recommended"><big><b>Scroll for more &#8230;</b> </big>\n This is the default activity for when the app opens and it contains listening recommendations
        based on the user\'s favorite genres/artists and the latest releases.
        When clicking on Youtube icon, the youtube app should open and search for the title of the now playing song.
       The like icon should add the now_playing song to favorites.
         The rest of the actions in the overflow menu should be self-explanatory.
        The functionality has not been completely implemented.
       The songs in the categories should actually be in a horizontal list view and dynamically loaded
      (maybe with a RecyclerView which I should learn to implement)
         onClick the song should start playing without changing the activity
       At that point the play button should change to pause button.
        Btw, the youtube and the web actions in the overflow menu are functional. However, I don\'t know how to fix the delay of the overflow
        menu tuning invisible when the navigation drawer is open.
    </string>
    <string name="lib_note"><big><b>Scroll for more &#8230;</b> </big>\n In this Activity the user will see al his/her songs in alphabetical order.
        In the upper part there will be the box with the playing song/last played song if the app has just been launched.
        I know that I didn\'t need to implement any functionality, but I couldn\'t resist the temptation, so I followed a small tutorial
        to implement some functionality: if you allow the app to have access to your media, your songs should appear in this activity.
        On touch the song starts playing. I still have some issues like I didn\'t manage to implement the AudioManager.OnAudioFocusChangeListener.
        Also, if you change the activity, the song stops playing.
    </string>
    <string name="radio_note">Here you can find the local stations and there is a section for favorite radios. The activity has no real
        functionality, except that when you tap on a button in the radio grid you get a toast message. The radio activity is special in that the
        \"Now Playing\" box (available while browsing all library related activities) will close and the playing song will stop.
    </string>
    <string name="playlist_note"><big><b>Scroll for more &#8230;</b> </big>\n In this Activity the user choose the playlist he wants to
        listen to. There is also an option to create a new playlist. Clicking the \"Create Playlist\" option should take the user to the library
        from where he/she can add songs. There is no functionality to this Activity.
    </string>
    <string name="select_favs">To add your favorite songs, touch and hold the song that you want to add and tap the star icon.
    </string>
    <string name="favorites_note"><big><b>Scroll for more &#8230;</b> </big>\n This activity will display in ListView the favorite songs of the user. Basically the user has to go
        to Library to select favorite songs. Honding on a song should open a special overflow menu (not built yet) with special options
        common to all songs such as add to favorites, delete, play, share, set as ringtone etc. As a sidenote, if a song is playing a
        special box will display on all songs related activities the \"Now Playing\" box showing the title of the song and a play/pause button.
    </string>


    <string name="playing_title">Princess of the Universe</string>
    <string name="playing_artist">Queen</string>
    <string name="mp3">.mp3</string>
    <string name="create_playlist">Create Playlist</string>
    <string name="radio_notification">You have no saved stations.</string>


</resources>
